Kai Schuyler Gonzalez

Boulder, CO • 720 496 5000 • linkedin.com/in/kaischuyler • kaischuyler.com

Software Engineer

I am a software engineer and designer with 2+ years of experience building applications for mobile and the web. Through personal and professional projects, as well as a wide range of coursework, I have a well-rounded view of the field of application development using tools like React, Node, the iOS SDK and Android.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CU Boulder Office of the Registrar • Boulder, Colorado, United States • 06/2021 - 01/2022 **Student Software Developer**

- Wrote software to assist with internal functions, mainly in the .NET framework using C#.
- Wrote multiple selenium applications that automated tasks for the office.
- Updated, debugged and documented legacy code used by the office.

CU Boulder Environmental Center • Boulder, Colorado • 10/2019 - 12/2020

Student Transportation Ambassador

- Assisted in the day to day internal operations of the office, mainly in the public transportation department.
- Helped organize the Environmental Center's ski bus for students.
- Promoted sustainability events and services on campus through multiple outreach programs.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science - BS in Computer Science

University of Colorado Boulder • Boulder, CO • 07/2018 - 08/2022

- Enrolled in the College of Engineering & Applied Science.
- Overall GPA: 3.26
- Major GPA: 3.6
- Minored in Creative Technology and Design.

SKILLS

.NET, AWS, Bash, C / C++, CSS, Docker, Front-End, Full-Stack, Git, HTML, iOS SDK, Java, JavaScript / Typescript, Kotlin, Node.js, OpenGL, Python, React.js, SQL, Swift, SwiftUI, UIKit, Unit Testing, Vue